Islam Nasser

Mobile Application Developer | Flutter and Dart |

Egypt, Suhag | +201155687867 | islam.alheky@gmail.com | 26 year's | Married

Summary

Flutter developer with over 3 years' experience, developed more than 10 Apps now on Google play, App Store, and am ready to be part of a reputable organization that provides steady professional growth along with job satisfaction and challenges and to make a valuable contribution to the success of the organization.

Education

Higher Institute of Computer Science & Management Technology Science and Management Technology.

Work Experience

Team leader Full time job at Be No.1

DECEMBER 2020 - JAUNARY 2022

work collaboratively with a good team of developers, and I'm the team leader there.

Flutter Mobile Application Developer Bart time job at Nazra

SEPTEMBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

Flutter Mobile Application Developer Bart time job at Layouti

JULE 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

A wonderful experience working on the development of the Etoy application to sell and exchange toys

Flutter Mobile Application Developer Full time job at Ai Technology

JULE 2018 - OCTOBER 2020

I've been working collaboratively with a good team of developers, and I've developed these apps that are above.

I have modified several previously developed projects in collaboration with a problem-solving team.

Programming Skills

- Dart programming language.
- Firebase Authentication.
- Strong knowledge in using Location & Google Maps & pleases.
- Strong knowledge in using Realtime Signal R.
- Strong knowledge in using Realtime Socket io.
- Patterns and architecture "MVC & MVVM".
- Use Localization to enable apps with multiple languages.
- Strong knowledge of using Provider state management.
- Create certificates and settings on the account of Apple developers.
- Publish apps on Google play & App store.
- Experience in REST APIs using Dart and JSON.
- Experience Push Notification using in Android and iOS.
- Object Oriented Mobile Software Development Experience.
- Ability to work independently and come up with innovative solutions.
- Strong Knowledge Using Photoshop, Acrobat, XCode, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Office.
- Good Communication Skills, and ability to working a team.
- Experience with version control systems such as Git, GitHub, Subversion.
- Management, Communication, Problem-solving, Design.
- Mobile Banking and payments, Mobile, Wallet "Visa, Mezza, Fawry".
- Familiar with Most Popular Operating Systems: Linux, Windows and MacOS.
- Applications for iPad, Android Tablets, and mobiles.

Work Experience

See the apps I've developed here Portfolio

Volunteering

04.2017 – 01.2019 | | IEEE student branch at Higher Institute of Computer Science & Management Technology Science and Management Technology.
03.2017 – 04.2018 | | Human resource Team at Higher Institute of Computer Science & Management Technology Science and Management Technology.

Languages

- English (Fair).
- Arabic (Native).